Didi, what is there in ICICI Pru Smart Insurance Plan
Plus that makes it the best?
What you see in this is what you get.
Meaning, you get your CTC in hand
?
No, tax is not deducted.
Whatever bonus is announced for you, you get it
in your account.
No, tax is deducted in that too.
Exactly this does not happen in ICICI Pro SIP Plus
because its returns are tax
free and there are zero charges as well.  That means you get the
return that you see.  So this
is just not right.   It
is the most correct.
ICICI [Music] Pro SIP Plus Buy Now
Trusted by over 20 crore Indians in 25
[Music] Years 3.21 lakh crore assets under
management and 3.24 lakh crore benefits
[Music] paid in 25 years.  Feel
responsible with ICICI Prudential Life Insurance.